# JUMOKE AMEENAH HAMEED

# MEDICAL OFFICER

☑ jummyhameed@gmail.com 📞 +2348157717192 👂 Flat 4, Block D2, 21st street, Games Village Estate, Abuja.

# **SUMMARY**

A young medical doctor, with excellent clinical as well as interpersonal skills and good exposure to clinical practice. Over the years, I have acquired experience in emergency medicine, primary care medicine and specialty care.

I endeavor to work according to established standards even under minimal supervision where my skills, knowledge and resourcefulness can be harnessed to contribute maximally into realizing organizational goals.

I value working as a team with other colleagues and health professionals, hence I ensure to cultivate and maintain a good rapport for an efficient healthcare delivery system.

# **EDUCATION**

#### University of Ilorin, Ilorin

MB;BS Medicine and Surgery 2019

#### Thomas Adewumi International College, Oko

West African Senior School Certificate 2012

## **EMPLOYMENT**

News Agency of Nigeria Clinic, MEDICAL OFFICER, Abuja, FCT Nigeria

June 2021 - Apr. 2022

- Full range of clinical care in a private clinic.
- · Out-patient care which include attending to medical emergencies and general medicine.

#### Gracevid Hospital, MEDICAL OFFICER, Kwara state, Nigeria

Aug. 2020 - May 2021

- Full range of clinical care in the private clinic.
- In and Out-patient care which includes management of emergency medical, pediatric and surgical cases.
- Provision of Antenatal care, Obstetric and Gynecological services.
- Preparation of patient's work-up for surgery, assisting surgical procedures, and ensuring optimal recovery of patients following surgery.

#### University of Ilorin Teaching Hospital, HOUSE OFFICER, Kwara state, Nigeria

May 2019 - Apr. 2020

- Involved in the management of medical and surgical conditions at Pediatric and Adult medical emergency Centres.
- First line respondent for all cases.
- · Performed minor surgical procedures.
- Provision of antenatal care and other Obstetric and Gynecological services.
- Involved in the collection, analysis, and presentation of health data.

# **SKILLS**

IT SKILLS: Proficient in the use of Microsoft Office Word and PowerPoint.

Excellent interpersonal and communication skills.

### OTHERS

NHCPS Basic life support certification (CME Eligible), Postgraduate institute of medicine	2020
NHCPS Pediatric Advanced Life Support certification(CME Eligible), Postgraduate institute of medicine	2020
Essentials of Global Health, Yale University on Coursera	2020
Epidemiology: The Basic Science of Public Health, The University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill on Coursera	2020
COVID-19: What You Need to Know (CME Eligible), Osmosis on Coursera	2020